http://www.ncnw.org/ncnw/terms-of-use

NCNW Brochure/Application & Handbook
R.E.A.C.H.
NCNW Brochure/Application & Handbook
R.E.A.C.H.
Scope of Terms of Use
This document sets forth the terms of use for the National Council of Negro Women (“NCNW”) website www.NCNW.org(“SITE”). Please read the following terms of use carefully. These terms of use govern your use of this site and all applications, software and services available on this site.
Acceptance of Terms
You acknowledge that you have read and agree to be bound by these terms of use and to comply with all applicable laws and regulations, including without limitation U.S. export and re-export technical data exported from the United States or the country in which you reside. You further agree to comply with all local laws, regulations and rules regarding online conduct and acceptable content. You represent you have the legal authority to accept these terms of use on behalf of yourself or any party you represent. If you do not agree to these terms of use, do not use this site in any manner.
Description of Site
“SITE” encompasses NCNW’s website and all of its content and policies, any modifications, updates, enhancements, revisions, new features, and/or the addition of any new web properties. NCNW reserves the right to make any SITE changes at any time and without prior notice.
Modifications
NCNW reserves the right to revise, supplement, update, delete and change these Terms of Use at any time at its sole discretion and without notice to you. All Terms of Use changes are effective immediately upon being posted. Your continued use of this SITE after any changes to these Terms of Use will mean you accept those changes. NCNW may also change or impose fees for products and services provided through the SITE at any time in its sole discretion.
NCNW Privacy Policy
NCNW’s privacy policy governs the use of information collected from or provided by you at the SITE. For more information, see our full privacy policy for this SITE.
Site Ownership
The SITE, including all text, logos or graphic images appearing therein, and any and all intellectual property rights associated with this SITE and its contents are the sole property of NCNW, its affiliates or third parties. The content is protected by copyright and other laws in both the United States and other countries. Elements of the SITE are also protected by trade dress, trade secret, unfair competition, and other laws and may not be copied or imitated in whole or in part. All graphics, icons, and other items that appear on the SITE are trademarks, service marks, trade dress and/or copyrighted works (“Intellectual Property”) of NCNW, its affiliates or other entities that have granted NCNW the right and license to use such Intellectual Property and may not be used or interfered with in any manner without the express written consent of NCNW. Except as expressly provided herein, NCNW does not grant you an express or implied right to NCNW’s or any third party’s Intellectual Property. The information on the SITE is intended to provide corporate, product, or service information only and may not be used for any other purposes.
Site Use Restrictions
THE UNAUTHORIZED COPYING, DISPLAYING OR OTHER USE OF ANY CONTENT FROM THIS SITE IS A VIOLATION OF LAW.
The SITE is for your personal and non-commercial use only. You will not (i) post on or transmit to the SITE any defamatory, libelous, obscene, pornographic, profane, threatening, or unlawful materials or any materials that could constitute or encourage conduct that would be considered a criminal offense or give rise to civil liability, whether under statute, common law or equitable principles, or otherwise violate any law; (ii) copy, reproduce, modify, lease, loan, sell, create derivative works from, upload, transmit, or distribute the intellectual property of the SITE in any way without NCNW’s or the appropriate third party’s prior written permission or (iii) use the SITE in any manner that violates any applicable laws, regulations, orders, or other restrictions.
Trademarks and Service Marks
There may be a number of proprietary logos, service marks, trademarks, slogans and product designations found on this SITE, including but not limited to: NCNW name and seal. Other trademarks displayed on this SITE through links to other sites are the property of the respective trademark owners. By making these marks available on this SITE, NCNW does not confer upon you any of NCNW’s or any third party’s intellectual property rights. No NCNW trademark may be used as a hyperlink without NCNW’s prior written permission.
Copyright Trademark Notices
All content of NCNW’s SITE is: Copyright © 2018 The National Council of Negro Women.
All Rights Reserved.
Indemnification
You agree to defend, indemnify, and hold
NCNW harmless from and against any and all claims, damages, costs and expenses, including attorneys’ fees, arising from or related to your use of the SITE.
Links to Third Party Websites Are Not Endorsements
This SITE may provide links to other third-party World Wide Web sites or resources. NCNW makes no representations or warranties whatsoever about any other website which you may access through this SITE. Because NCNW has no control over such sites and resources, you acknowledge and agree that NCNW is not responsible for the availability of such external sites or resources and is not responsible or liable for any content, advertising, products, services or other materials on or available from such sites or resources. It is your responsibility to take precautions to ensure that whatever you select for your use is free of viruses, worms, Trojan horses and other items of a destructive nature. References on this SITE to any names, marks, products or services of any third parties or hypertext links to third party sites or information are provided solely as a convenience to you, and do not constitute or imply an endorsement, sponsorship or recommendation of, or affiliation with the third party or its products and services. NCNW shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with use of or reliance on any such third-party content, products or services available on or through any such site or resource.
Notices and Procedure for Making Claims of Copyright Infringement
NCNW will investigate notices of copyright infringement and take appropriate actions under the Digital Millennium Copyright Act, 17 U.S.C. § 512(c)(2) (“DMCA”). Pursuant to the DMCA, written notification of claimed copyright infringement must be submitted to the following Designated Agent for NCNW in accordance with the DMCA: NCNW, Attention DMCA Designated Agent, NCNW National Headquarters, 633 Pennsylvania Avenue, NW
Washington, DC 20004, webmaster@NCNW.org.
Email/Feedback Property of NCNW
You may choose to use email to communicate with NCNW. If you choose to email NCNW, know that the Internet is not secure or private, unauthorized people may be able to intercept and read the mail you send to NCNW or mail NCNW sends to you. Since email can be used to spread viruses, you should install and maintain virus protection software on your PC. To the extent permitted by applicable law, any comments or materials (collectively “Feedback”) sent to NCNW including but not limited to questions, submissions, suggestions, ideas, postings, comments or the like shall become the property of NCNW upon receipt. NCNW shall have no obligation of any kind with respect to such Feedback and shall be free to modify, copy, perform, publish, transmit, reproduce, use, exhibit, disclose, display, transform, copyright, create derivative works, distribute the Feedback to others and otherwise exploit the Feedback without limitation. Further, NCNW shall be free to use any ideas, concepts, know-how or techniques contained in such Feedback for any purpose whatsoever, including but not limited to developing, manufacturing and marketing products incorporating such information.
Limitation of Liability
NCNW WILL NOT BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANY THIRD PARTY FOR ANY DAMAGES OF ANY KIND ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO THE USE OR THE INABILITY TO USE THIS SITE, ITS CONTENT OR LINKS, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO LOSS OF PROFITS OR OTHER DAMAGES CAUSED BY OR RELATED TO ERRORS, OMISSION, INTERRUPTIONS, DEFECTS, DELAY IN OPERATION OR TRANSMISSION, COMPUTER VIRUS, LINE FAILURE, AND ALL OTHER DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL INCIDENTAL, EXEMPLARY OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OF ANY KIND WHETHER UNDER THESE TERMS OF USE, STATUTE, REGULATION, COMMON LAW PRECEDENT OR DOCTRINE, EVEN IF NCNW HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES OR WAS NEGLIGENT. IN JURISDICTIONS THAT PROHIBIT THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, NCNW’S LIABILITY IS LIMITED TO THE GREATEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW. NOTWITHSTANDING THE FOREGOING, NCNW’S TOTAL LIABILITY TO YOU FOR ALL LOSSES, DAMAGES, AND CAUSES OF ACTION, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THOSE BASED ON CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING OUT OF YOUR USE OF THIS SITE, ITS CONTENT OR LINKS, SHALL NOT EXCEED THE AMOUNT YOU PAID TO ACCESS THIS SITE.
THE INFORMATION ON THIS SITE, INCLUDING TEXT, IMAGES, AND LINKS, AND THE INFORMATION ON ANY WEBSITES, WHETHER AFFILIATED OR UNAFFILIATED WITH NCNW, WHICH YOU MAY VISIT THROUGH THE SITE, IS PROVIDED “AS IS” BY NCNW AS A CONVENIENCE TO ALL USERS, WITHOUT REPRESENTATION OR WARRANTY OF ANY KIND TO YOU OR ANY THIRD PARTY, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO, ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES (I) OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE; (II) OF INFORMATIONAL CONTENT OR ACCURACY; (III) OF NON-INFRINGEMENT; (IV) OF QUIET ENJOYMENT; (V) OF TITLE; (VI) THAT THE SITE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE; (VII) THAT ANY DEFECTS OR ERRORS IN THE SITE WILL BE CORRECTED; (VIII) THAT THE SITE OR THE SERVER THAT MAKES IT AVAILABLE ARE FREE FROM VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS OR (IX) THAT THE SITE IS COMPATIBLE WITH ANY PARTICULAR HARDWARE OR SOFTWARE PLATFORM. EFFORTS BY NCNW TO MODIFY THE SITE SHALL NOT BE DEEMED A WAIVER OF THESE LIMITATIONS.
Governing Law
These Terms of Use are entered into and granted in Washington, D.C. and shall be governed by and interpreted pursuant to the laws of the United States of America, excluding any law or conflicts or law principle that would apply the law of another jurisdiction.
You expressly agree that the exclusive jurisdiction for any dispute, controversy or claim arising out of or in connection with these Terms of Use shall be filed only in the federal or state court with competent jurisdiction located in Washington, D.C. You consent to the exercise of personal jurisdiction by such courts in any such action. If any part of these Terms and Conditions is unlawful, void, or unenforceable, that part will be deemed severable and will not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining provisions.
Entire Agreement
These Terms of Use constitute the entire agreement between you and NCNW and govern your use of the SITE, superseding any prior agreements between you and NCNW relating to your use of this SITE.
Use of Communication Services
The NCNW SITE may in the future contain bulletin board services, chat areas, news groups, forums, communities, personal web pages, calendars, and/or other message or communication facilities designed to enable you to communicate with the public at large or with a group (collectively, “Communication Services”). You agree to use the Communication Services only to post, send and receive messages and material that are proper and related to the particular Communication Service. By way of example, and not as a limitation, you agree that when using a Communication Service, you will not:
Defame, abuse, harass, stalk, threaten or otherwise violate the legal rights (such as rights of privacy and publicity) of others.
Publish, post, upload, distribute or disseminate any inappropriate, profane, defamatory, infringing, obscene, indecent or unlawful topic, name, material or information.
Upload files that contain software or other material protected by intellectual property laws (or by rights of privacy of publicity) unless you own or control the rights thereto or have received all necessary consents.
Upload files that contain viruses, corrupted files, or any other similar software or programs that may damage the operation of another’s computer.
Advertise or offer to sell or buy any goods or services for any business purpose, unless such Communication Service specifically allows such messages.
Conduct or forward surveys, contests, pyramid schemes or chain letters.
Download any file posted by another user of a Communication Service that you know, or reasonably should know, cannot be legally distributed in such manner.
Falsify or delete any author attributions, legal or other proper notices or proprietary designations or labels of the origin or source of software or other material contained in a file that is uploaded.
Restrict or inhibit any other user from using and enjoying the Communication Services.
Violate any code of conduct or other guidelines which may be applicable for any particular Communication Service.
Harvest or otherwise collect information about others, including e-mail addresses, without their consent.
Violate any applicable laws or regulations.
NCNW has no obligation to monitor the Communication Services. However, NCNW reserves the right to review materials posted to a Communication Service and to remove any materials in its sole discretion. NCNW reserves the right to terminate your access to any or all of the Communication Services at any time, without notice, for any reason whatsoever.
NCNW reserves the right at all times to disclose any information as necessary to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, or to edit, refuse to post or to remove any information or materials, in whole or in part, in NCNW’s sole discretion.
Always use caution when giving out any personally identifying information about yourself or other people in any Communication Service. NCNW does not control or endorse the content, messages or information found in any Communication Service and, therefore, NCNW specifically disclaims any liability with regard to the Communication Services and any actions resulting from your participation in any Communication Service.
By posting, uploading, inputting, providing or submitting your submission to NCNW, you are granting NCNW, its affiliated companies and necessary sub licensees permission to use your submission in connection with the operation of their Internet businesses including, without limitation, the rights to: copy, distribute, transmit, publicly display, publicly perform, reproduce, edit, translate and reformat your submission; and to publish your name in connection with your submission.
No compensation will be paid with respect to the use of your submission, as provided herein. NCNW is under no obligation to post or use any submission you may provide and may remove any submission at any time in NCNW’s sole discretion.
By posting, uploading, inputting, providing or submitting your submission you warrant and represent that you own or otherwise control all of the rights to your submission as described in this section including, without limitation, all the rights necessary for you to provide, post, upload, input or submit the submissions.
Message Boards
NCNW does not monitor message boards hosted on its SITE. The content of message boards is the sole responsibility of the person supplying the content, and NCNW assumes no liability related to the content of such boards. All messages posted on NCNW message boards are non-confidential and will be treated as such.
Termination
NCNW reserves the right to terminate at any time, at its sole discretion, the SITE and/or your use of the SITE.
Unlawful or Prohibited Use
Possible evidence of use of this SITE for illegal purposes will be provided to law enforcement authorities. Please report any violations of these Terms of Use to NCNW at webmaster@NCNW.org.
Service Contact
webmaster@NCNW.org
PRIVACY POLICY
National Council of Negro Women (“NCNW”) values the protection of individual privacy. This document sets forth NCNW’s online privacy policy (“privacy policy”) for the website www.NCNW.org (“site”). By using the site, you the user (“you”) indicate that you have read and agree to be bound by this privacy policy. If you do not agree to this privacy policy, do not use the site in any manner. This privacy policy does not govern privacy practices associated with offline activities.
Thank you for visiting the site. We are committed to the privacy of our visitors. We collect no personal information about you when you visit the site unless you choose to provide that information to us and we do not use personal information other than to process your request that required you to submit personal information. We do not make any visitor-provided information available to third parties.
Here is how we handle information about your visit to our Web site.
Information collected and stored automatically
If you do nothing during your visit but browse through the site, read pages, or download information, we will gather and store certain information about your visit automatically. This information does not identify you personally. We automatically collect and store information concerning your visit:
The Internet domain (for example, “xcompany.com” if you use a private Internet access account or “yourschool.edu” if you connect from a university’s domain);
Your IP address (an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web) from which you access the site;
The type of browser and operating system used to access the site;
The date and time you access the site;
The pages you visit within the site; and
If you linked to our Web site from another Web site, the address of that website.
Information that you voluntarily provide:
On certain pages of NCNW website, we may ask you to voluntarily provide personal data such as your name, mailing address, email address, credit card information, telephone number and similar information.
That information is collected when you:
Donate to NCNW.
Purchase an NCNW membership.
Sign to receive NCNW alerts.
Sign NCNW petitions.
If you provide us with personally identifiable information, for example, by sending an e-mail or by filling out a form and submitting it through the site, we use that information to respond to your message and to help us provide you with the information and services that you request. All uses of that information are described on the web page containing the form.
Submitting voluntary information constitutes your consent to the use of the information for the stated purpose. When you click the “Submit” button on any of the web forms found on the site, you are indicating your voluntary consent for us to use of the information you submit for the purpose stated.
If you no longer wish to receive emails from NCNW, you can click the unsubscribe link located at the bottom of NCNW email.
In addition, if you would like to review and/or update your personal information being collected by NCNW, you may contact NCNW Web Developer and Graphic Artist Sandra Green at sgreen@ncnw.org or (202) 737-0120.
Links to other sites:
The site contains links to various other private organizations. Once you link to another website, you are then subject to the privacy policies of the new website. We cannot control nor are we responsible for any such third party collection or use of your personal information. It is always a good idea to read the Privacy Policy of any website you visit.
Children:
The Site is a general audience site which is neither designed nor intended to collect personal information from children who are under the age of 13. In order to ensure compliance with the provisions of the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, children under the age of 13 should not provide any personal information to the Site.
Security:
We use commercially reasonable efforts to ensure that any information you give to us is stored and maintained in secure servers and not publicly accessible.
NCNW protects personal data by only allowing limited, authorized personnel to have access to such personal data.
NCNW maintains an encrypted firewall to protect such personal data. NCNW’s software provider has level one payment card industry compliance to ensure that online credit transactions are secure.
NCNW has technical safeguards such as “firewalls, virus and intrusion detection, and authentication protocols.” However, despite our best security efforts, no data transmission or storage can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.
Cookies:
We may use cookies from time to time to allow us to automate access and the data entry functions of the Site such as to tailor the Site to your preferences or interests, customize promotions or marketing, or identify which areas of the Site are more popular. A cookie is a small, unique text file that a website can send to your computer hard drive when you visit that site. We do not make any cookie information available to third parties. Most web browsers can either alert you to the use of cookies or refuse to accept cookies entirely. If you do not want us to deploy cookies in your browser, you can set your browser to reject cookies or to notify you when a website tries to put a cookie on your computer. Rejecting cookies may affect your ability to use of some of the products and/or services at the Site.
Privacy Policy Changes:
We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time at its sole discretion and without notice to you. All Privacy Policy changes are effective immediately. Your continued use of the Site following any Privacy Policy changes will mean you accept those changes.
Contact Information:
If you have difficulty obtaining information from the site, please contact us to get the material in another format. You should provide the URL of the site referencing that information. If you have any comments, or suggestions for improvement, please contact webmaster@NCNW.org.
REFUND POLICY
Product Sold
Upon our receipt of the returned product, we will replace or exchange the product or issue you a refund in the form of your original payment should you wish to return it.
Product in Exchange for a donation
Upon receipt of the returned product, we will replace or exchange the product.
Please note that due to current tax laws, donations made in exchange for a product are unable to be refunded.
Donations
Donations made to NCNW made within the previous thirty (30) days will be refunded and future recurring donations canceled upon written notification received by mail or email with the appropriate documents verifying that the requester and donor is the same person.
If sent by United States mail, the address is 633 Pennsylvania Avenue, NW Washington, DC 20004.
If sent via email, send to support@NCNW.org.
Donations made for event or ticket purchases are not refundable.
If you have made a recurring donation, you may log on using the email address you entered and the password you selected at the time of the donation and either cancel or modify the amount of the recurring donation.
STEAM Education
Eliminate Barriers
Economic Empowerment & Entrepreneurship
Media Information & News Releases
Like us on facebook
Get connected:
HeadquartersNational Council Negro Women, Inc.633 Pennsylvania Avenue, NW Washington, DC 20004P: 202-737-0120F: N/AFIND THE SECTION NEAREST YOU
Copyright © 2018
National Council Negro Women, Inc.
Contact Us
Terms of Use
Home
Vireo Enterprise an Intersoft Group Solution
